[
    {
        "question": "ğŸ¥·",
        "response": "ğŸ¥·ğŸ¿"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ‘",
        "response": "ğŸ‘ğŸ¿"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ‘Š",
        "response": "ğŸ‘ŠğŸ¿"
    },
    {
        "question": "âœŠ",
        "response": "âœŠğŸ¿"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ¤›",
        "response": "ğŸ¤›ğŸ¿"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ¤œ",
        "response": "ğŸ¤œğŸ¿"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ«·",
        "response": "ğŸ«·ğŸ¿"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ«¸",
        "response": "ğŸ«¸ğŸ¿"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ¤",
        "response": "ğŸ¤ğŸ¿"
    },
    {
        "question": "âœŒï¸",
        "response": "âœŒğŸ¿"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ«°",
        "response": "ğŸ«°ğŸ¿"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ¤Ÿ",
        "response": "ğŸ¤ŸğŸ¿"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ‘‡",
        "response": "ğŸ‘‡ğŸ¿"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ’ª",
        "response": "ğŸ’ªğŸ¿"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ«µ",
        "response": "ğŸ«µğŸ¿"
    },
    {
        "question": "âœï¸",
        "response": "âœğŸ¿"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ¤",
        "response": "ğŸ¤ğŸ¿"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ¤Œ",
        "response": "ğŸ¤ŒğŸ¿"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ«´",
        "response": "ğŸ«´ğŸ¿"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ«³",
        "response": "ğŸ«³ğŸ¿"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ‘®â€â™‚ï¸",
        "response": "ğŸ‘®ğŸ¿â€â™‚ï¸"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ§•",
        "response": "ğŸ§•ğŸ¿"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ‘¨â€ğŸ«",
        "response": "ğŸ‘¨ğŸ¿â€ğŸ«"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ‘¨â€ğŸ“",
        "response": "ğŸ‘¨ğŸ¿â€ğŸ“"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ‘",
        "response": "ğŸ‘ğŸ¿"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ§‘â€ğŸš€",
        "response": "ğŸ§‘ğŸ¿â€ğŸš€"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ•µï¸â€â™‚ï¸",
        "response": "ğŸ•µğŸ¿â€â™‚ï¸"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ«¶",
        "response": "ğŸ«¶ğŸ¿"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ™Œ",
        "response": "ğŸ™ŒğŸ¿"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ¤",
        "response": "ğŸ«±ğŸ¿â€ğŸ«²ğŸ¿"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ‘",
        "response": "ğŸ‘ğŸ¿"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ‘¨â€ğŸ’»",
        "response": "ğŸ‘¨ğŸ¿â€ğŸ’»"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ¦¸â€â™‚ï¸",
        "response": "ğŸ¦¸ğŸ¿â€â™‚ï¸"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ§™â€â™‚ï¸",
        "response": "ğŸ§™ğŸ¿â€â™‚ï¸"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ§â€â™€ï¸",
        "response": "ğŸ§ğŸ¿â€â™€ï¸"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ§šâ€â™‚ï¸",
        "response": "ğŸ§šğŸ¿â€â™‚ï¸"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ§œâ€â™€ï¸",
        "response": "ğŸ§œğŸ¿â€â™€ï¸"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ™†",
        "response": "ğŸ™†ğŸ¿"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ™…",
        "response": "ğŸ™…ğŸ¿"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ’â€â™‚ï¸",
        "response": "ğŸ’ğŸ¿â€â™‚ï¸"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ™…â€â™‚ï¸",
        "response": "ğŸ™…ğŸ¿â€â™‚ï¸"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ’†",
        "response": "ğŸ’†ğŸ¿"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ§–â€â™‚ï¸",
        "response": "ğŸ§–ğŸ¿â€â™‚ï¸"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ§â€â™‚ï¸",
        "response": "ğŸ§ğŸ¿â€â™‚ï¸"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ‘©â€â¤ï¸â€ğŸ‘¨",
        "response": "ğŸ‘©ğŸ¿â€â¤ï¸â€ğŸ‘¨ğŸ¿"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ§‘â€ğŸ¦¯",
        "response": "ğŸ§‘ğŸ¿â€ğŸ¦¯"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ•º",
        "response": "ğŸ•ºğŸ¿"
    },
    {
        "question": "ğŸ’‡â€â™‚ï¸",
        "response": "ğŸ’‡ğŸ¿â€â™‚ï¸"
    },
    {
       "question": "ğŸ«´",
       "response": "ğŸ«´ğŸ¿"
}
]
